{
    "subject": "resource/Dusk_(Andrew_Hill_album)",
    "predicate": "ontology/artist",
    "object": "resource/Andrew_Hill",
    "human_readable": "Dusk is an album by Andrew Hill.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8901214599609375,
            "question": "Where can you listen to Andrew Hill's album Dusk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7616130709648132,
            "question": "Is Dusk a musical album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7171124219894409,
            "question": "Who created the album Dusk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6923016309738159,
            "question": "What is the name of Andrew Hill's album?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6408293843269348,
            "question": "Can you name an album by Andrew Hill?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.635224461555481,
            "question": "What year was the album Dusk released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5716556906700134,
            "question": "Are there any famous songs on the album Dusk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2585615813732147,
            "question": "What genre of music might Dusk belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19502755999565125,
            "question": "What type of artistic work is Dusk?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07304432988166809,
            "question": "Who are some other musicians who have created albums?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dusk is an album by Andrew Hill.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7210_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of artistic work is Dusk?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7210_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music might Dusk belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7210_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous songs on the album Dusk?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7210_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7210_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to \"Dusk\" as an album by Andrew Hill, confirming the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}